// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What do you call a file containing a program written in a high-level programming language?",
    answer: "A source file",
    options: [
      "A machine file",
      "A code file",
      "A target file",
      "A source file"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The \n digraph forces the print() function to:",
    answer: "break the output line",
    options: [
      "stop its execution",
      "duplicate the character next to the digragh",
      "break the output line",
      "output exactly two characters: \ and n"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "z = y = x = 1 print(x, y, z, sep='*')",
    answer: "1*1*1",
    options: [
      "1 1 1",
      "x*y*z",
      "1*1*1",
      "x y z"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following variable names are illegal? ",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "true",
      "anD",
      "TRUE",
      "True"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The ** operator:",
    answer: "performs exponentiation",
    options: [
      "does not exist",
      "performs duplicated multiplication ",
      "performs exponentiation",
      "perform floating-point multiplication"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The 80 prefix means that the number after it is denoted as:",
    answer: "octal",
    options: [
      "hexadecimal",
      "octal",
      "decimal",
      "binary"
    ]
  },
      {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The meaning of the keyword parameter is determined by:",
    answer: "the argument’s name specified along with is value",
    options: [
      "its value",
      "the argument’s name specified along with is value",
      "its connection with exiting variables",
      "its position within the argument list"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "An operator able to check whether two values are equal is code as:",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "=",
    "!=",
      "==",
      "==="
    ]
  },
    {  
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the sys.stdout stream normally associated with?",
    answer: "The screen",
    options: [
      "The printer",
      "A null device",
      "The keyboard",
      "The screen"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The Exception class contains a property named args -what is it?",
    answer: "A tuple",
    options: [
      "A dictionary ",
      "A list",
      "A string",
      "A tuple"
    ]
  },
];
